A Finding Aid to the Linda Farris Gallery Records, 1969-1995, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Linda Farris Gallery records
1969-1995
Archives of American Art
Linda Farris Gallery
Farris, Linda
AAA.lindfarr
Archival Resource Key
13.4 Linear feet 13 Boxes, 1 sol, 1 ov folder
The records of Seattle's avant-garde Linda Farris Gallery measure 13.4 linear feet and date from 1969-1995. The bulk of the records consist of artists' and exhibition files. Also found are gallery business correspondence, administrative files, event files, reference files, records of sales, scattered legal files, the personal papers of gallery owner Linda Farris, and printed materials.
Scope and Contents
The records of Seattle's avant-garde Linda Farris Gallery measure 13.4 linear feet and date from 1969-1995. The bulk of the records consist of artists' and exhibition files. Also found are gallery business correspondence, administrative files, event files, reference files, records of sales, scattered legal files, the personal papers of gallery owner Linda Farris, and printed materials. Business correspondence is with galleries, dealers, publishers, museums, and other businesses. Administrative files are varied and include advertising and promotion materials, exhibition schedules, mailing lists, guest books, a scrapbook, and gallery history.
Artists' files are found for many contemporary American artists that interested Linda Farris or were represented by the gallery. The contents of each file vary but many include photographs and slides, writings, correspondence, and printed materials. Files for Lynda Barry, Grisha Brusking, Charles Clough, Ronnie Landfield, Charles Luce, Michael Lucerno, Sherry Markovitz, Louise Nevelson, Barbara Noah, and Beverly Pepper are particularly rich. Exhibition files are for Linda Farris Gallery exhibitions and include printed materials, correspondence, loan and consignment agreements, and photographs.
Event files cover anniversary celebrations, lectures, panel discussions, and receptions. There are 17 sound cassette recordings of "Art Now" lectures and "Focus" panel discussions. Scattered reference files contain collected materials on subjects of interest to the gallery. There are scattered financial, sales, and legal files. Sales records cover 1970-1979.
Linda Farris' personal papers contain printed materials about her and the gallery and other materials concerning her professional and curatorial work outside of the gallery. There is also a transcript of an oral history with Farris and a news interview.
Printed materials include published books and magazines, clippings and exhibition catalogs and announcements.
Photographs are scattered throughout adminstrative files, exhibition files, event files, and Linda Farris' personal papers.
Related Materials
An oral history interview with Linda Farris conducted in 1975 by Sally Swenson, is located in the University of Washington University Libraries Digital Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Linda Farris Gallery records were donated to the Archives of American Art by owner Linda Farris in 1995 at the time she closed the gallery.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Biographical / Historical
The Linda Farris Gallery was Seattle's leading venue for contemporary art during its twenty-five years of operation.
Linda Farris opened Gallery East in Bellevue in 1970, and a year later moved to Pioneer Square in Seattle, changing the name to Linda Farris Gallery in 1973. The gallery continued to present contemporary art there until closing in December 1995. Art dealer Linda Farris began representing a group of promising artists, all graduates of the University of Washington. Greg Kucera of the Greg Kucera Gallery noted in an article for the Seattle Weekly, "Their work could be loosely seen as a movement, complete with aesthetic interrelationships, convenient marriages, an unintelligible manifesto in the form of Dennis Evans' quirky pronouncements…" From the same article he states, "Her avant-garde gallery changed forever the nature of being an art dealer in Seattle." It was among the three or four most influential galleries in the Pacific Northwest.
The gallery held exhibitions of many nationally known contemporary artists, including Sam Francis, Louise Nevelson, and Robert Rauschenberg, as well as Northwest artists Jeffrey Bishop, Dennis Evans, Sherry Markovitz, Nancy Mee, Norie Sato, and Patti Warashina. The latter group started with the gallery and remained loyal at the time of its closing in 1995.
Art dealer, collector and free-lance curator Linda B. Farris (1944-2005), a native of San Francisco and a graduate of the University of California, Berkeley (1966), was an active participant in and style setter for the Seattle art world for the twenty-five years she was in business. As a member of the art community she actively supported the Henry Art Gallery at the University of Washington, Pilchuck Glass School, and Seattle Art Museum's Contemporary Art Council, and served on the boards of directors of Henry Art Gallery and Factory Visual Arts. Farris curated "Eight Seattle Artists" in 1981 for the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art and "Self Portraits" in 1983 for the Los Angeles Municipal Art Gallery. She also led the movement to keep Henry Moore's "Vertebrae" from leaving Seattle, and instituted a series of talks, panel discussions, performances, and tours in her gallery, and in and around Seattle.
This note draws heavily on the Archives of American Art's West Coast Regional Collector Paul Karlstrom's collection description written upon acquisition of the papers.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 8 series.
Missing Title
Series 1: Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated (Box 1; .7 linear feet)
Series 2: Administrative files, 1970-1995, undated (Box 1-2, 14; 1 linear feet)
Series 3: Artists and Exhibition files, 1969-1995, undated (Box 2-9, 15; 6.6 linear feet)
Series 4: Events files, 1971-1990, undated (Box 9, 14; 0.6 linear feet)
Series 5: Reference files, 1969-1994, undated (Box 9-10; 0.6 linear feet)
Series 6: Financial, Sales and Legal files, 1970-1995 (Box 10; 0.4 linear feet)
Series 7: Linda Farris Papers, 1972-1995 (Box 10-11; .9 linear feet)
Series 8: Printed Materials, 1970-1995 (Box 11-14; 2 linear feet)
Interviews; Avant-garde (Aesthetics); Scrapbooks; Lectures; Art -- Washington (State) -- Exhibitions; Art, Modern -- 20th century -- Washington (State) -- Seattle; Artists -- Northwestern States; Photographs; Sound recordings; Visitors' books; Transcripts; Art galleries, Commercial -- Washington (State); Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988; Lucero, Michael, 1953-; Markovitz, Sherry; Landfield, Ronnie, 1947-; Luce, Charles, 1947-; Pepper, Beverly; Bruskin, Grisha, 1945-; Noah, Barbara; Clough, Charles, 1951-; Barry, Lynda, 1956-
- Correspondence, 1975-1991, undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.7 Linear feet Box 1
  Arrangement
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of correspondence.
  Scope and Contents
  General business correspondence is between owner Linda Farris and galleries, dealers, publishers, museums, and other businesses; some with enclosures such as photographs and brochures. Topics covered include orders and payments for art works, invitations and exhibition announcements from other galleries, and general business issues. Additional correspondence is found in other series as well.
  - Current Clients, 1977-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Current Clients, 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Current Clients, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dealers, 1975-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Dealers and Inventory, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General, 1972-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Museums, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Administrative files, 1970-1995, undated; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Box 1-2, 14
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  Administrative records include advertising and promotion materials, mailing lists, owner's notes, exhibition schedules, forms, corporate leads and information, guest books, gallery history information, including opening, early years and closing, office wall materials (space devoted to arts information on wall of gallery), photographs and slides of the gallery and Linda Farris, and a scrapbook on various artists for client use.
  - Blank forms, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Leads, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Corporate Notebook Originals, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions Out of Gallery, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Schedules, 1987, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - Gallery and Linda Farris Photographs, 1971-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gallery and Linda Farris Slides, 1982, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gallery Closing - Auction, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gallery Closing - Goodbye, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gallery East - Early Years, 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gallery East First Year, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guest Book, 1976-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Invitation Ideas, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Items from Gallery Office Wall, 1973-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Lists, 1977-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Messages, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Messages, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Notes - Idea and Project Books, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Overseas Color Printing - Ruffner et al, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Promotion Booklet, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Materials - Miscellaneous, 1983-1988, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Publicity Promotions, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Reception Invitation, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Rental of Artist Installation Program, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook - for Client Use, 1972-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook - for Client Use, Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Upcoming Exhibitions Out of Gallery, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Oversized from Box 2, Folder 8, Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
- Artists and Exhibition files, 1969-1995, undated; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 6.6 Linear feet Box 2-9, OV 15
  Arranged in two subseries:
  Missing Title
  Subseries 1: Named files, 1969-1995, undated
  Subseries 2: Exhibitions files, 1975-1995, undated
  The Artists and Exhibition files contain a wide variety of materials created and collected by Linda Farris Gallery on artists and exhibitions. Artists' files for Lynda Barry, Grisha Brusking, Charles Clough, Ronnie Landfield, Charles Luce, Michael Lucerno, Sherry Markovitz, Louise Nevelson, Barbara Noah, and Beverly Pepper are particularly rich. Notable exhibitions covered include "My Neighbor the Kingdom" with nearly 30 artists participating in an exhibit coordinated with the opening of the stadium, "Self Portraits" with works by 47 artists, including Andy Warhol, Robert Mapplethorpe, and Edvard Munch, and "Eight Seattle Artists" held at the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art.
  - Artists' Files, 1969-1995, undated; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by surname.
    Artists' files contain a wide variety of materials either created by or collected and collated by Linda Farris Gallery, such as photographs and slides, correspondence, exhibition catalogs, writings, publicity, and price lists.
    - Nicolas Africano "Portraits of Rebecca" (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Robert Arneson, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Lynda Barry "Naked Ladies"(1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Lynda Barry, 1981-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Lynda Barry, 1985-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Lynda Barry, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Keith Beckley "New Work" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Lynda Benglis "Sculpture and Silk Paintings" (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Billy Al Bengston "Honolulu Watercolors" (1982), 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Jeffrey Bishop "New Paintings" (1982), 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Harry Bowers "Color Photographs" (1978), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Keith Boyle "Collage Drawings" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Judy Lerner Brice, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Christopher Brown "new drawings, monotypes & prints" (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Grisha Bruskin "Paintings, Scultures, Prints" (1993), 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
    - Guy Buffet, 1969, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Marsha Burns, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Christo Javacheff, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Charles Clough "Love Songs / Dance Tunes" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Charles Clough "New Work" (1981), 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Charles Clough "Recent Paintings" (1980), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Chema Cobo "New Paintings - Works on Paper" (1984), 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Carolyn Cole, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Alison Collins, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Walter Cotten "New Works" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Ford Crull "New Paintings and Works on Paper" (1988), 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Laddie John Dill "New Paintings, Drawings and Wall Reliefs" (1984), 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Dennis Evans "The Four Forces of the Universe" (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Dennis Evans "Seven Garments and Seven Lies for the Passing of Days" (1980), 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - John Edwards Rajanen "New Paintings" (1976), 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Tom Fawkes "Paintings Watercolors Constructions" (undated), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sam Francis "Selected Lithographs Large Scale Etchings" (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Richard Francisco "New Works" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Richard Francisco "Recent Paintings" (1980), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Ann Gardner "Familiar Rhythms" (1992), 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Ann Gardner "Positioning" (1995), 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nancy Genn "Handmade Paper Works" (1978), 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - David Gilhooly, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sam Gilliam "paintings, watercolors, prints" (1974), 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Robert Gonzales, 1974-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Mike Hascall "new paintings & drawings" (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Louise Hoeschen "New Paintings" (undated), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Louise Hoeschen "Recent Paintings" (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Louise Hoeschen "Recent Paintings and Drawings" (1981), 1979-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Tom Holland "New Paintings" (1979), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Tom Holland "New Works on Paper" (undated), 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Harold Hollingsworth "Paintings Drawings Books" (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Mel Katz "New Sculpture" (1982), 1981-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Mel Katz "Post Series" (1977), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Mel Katz "Selected Works 1972-1980" (1980), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Mel Katz "Wall Works & Paper Pieces" (1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Ronnie Landfield "New Paintings" (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Ronnie Landfield "New Paintings" (1987), 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Ronnie Landfield "New Paintings & Works on Paper" (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Ronnie Landfield " Recent Paintings" (1979), 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Carolyn Law "Sculptural Installations" (1979), 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Charles Luce "An Exhibition of New Works" (1976), 1975-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Charles Luce "Fans" (1979), 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Charles Luce "Wind Silhouettes and Related Shadow Tales" (1979), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Michael Lucerno "New Sculpture" (1982), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Michael Lucerno "New Sculture in Bronze" (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Michael Lucerno "Reclamation Series" (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Sherry Markovitz "Bucks and Does" (1981), 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Sherry Markovitz "Easy Targets" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Sherry Markovitz "Life Forms" (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Nancy Mee "The Architecture of the Spine" (1982), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Nancy Mee "New Sculpture" (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Lawrence Miller "oils & watercolors" (undated), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Peter Millet "New Paintings" (1981), 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Peter Millet "New Paintings and Drawings" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Michael Moore "Paintings" (1974), 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Margaret Moorman "recent Paintings and drawings" (1977), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Matt Mullican, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Louise Nevelson, 1969-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
    - Louise Nevelson - Print Portfolio "Celebration" (1980), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Louise Nevelson "Recent Wood Sculpture" (1978), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Barbara Noah, 1978-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Barbara Noah "No Net" (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Barbara Noah "Recent Works" (1978), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Barbara Noah "Tampering with Evidence" (1979), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Isamu Noguchi, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Kenneth Noland, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Nathan Oliviera "recent works on paper" (1973), 1963-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - Andy Ostheimer "Diorama"(1982), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
    - Mark Ota "Recent Paintings" (1980), 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Gertrude Pacific, 1972-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Harold Paris, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Beverly Pepper, 1974-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Beverly Pepper, 1974-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Mary Ann Peters "Silent Partners" (1983), 1978-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Bob Peterson "Seattle Discovered" (1977), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Richard Pettibone, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Robert Rauschenberg "hand collage and hand silkscreen on paper" (1979), 1976-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5-8)
    - Barbara Rogers "New Paintings and Works on Paper" (1976), 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Betye Saar, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Peter Santino "Recent Work" (1983), 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Norie Sato "Peripheral Vision and Other New Work" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Norie Sato "Image Decay" (1981) "Machine Memory" (1995) "Incidents of Interference" (1987), 1981, 1987, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Italo Scanga "New Sculpture and Works on Paper" (1986), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Barbara Schwartz "New Works" (1982), 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
    - Patrick Siler "Paintings" (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Julie Speidel "Bronze Sculpture" (1987) "Bronze Sculpture" (1990) "Open Ground" (1994), 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kim Steele, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Bruce Pitcairn Strachan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Merrily Tompkins "El Nino" (1987), 1984-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Andy Warhol "Ten Portraits of Jews of the Twentieth Century" (1980), 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Dan Webb "Without a Sound" (1995), 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - William Wiley, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Bing Wright, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition files, 1975-1995, undated; 3.2; Archival Resource Key
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by title.
    Exhibition files are for Linda Farris Gallery exhibitions and include announcements, brochures, clippings, correspondence, loan and consignment agreements, notes, press releases, price lists, posters, photographic materials, and background material. The amount of material varies widely from file to file.
    - ADAA "The Art Show" (1990), 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
    - "Artstore" (1993) (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Billy Al Bengston / Laddie John Dill / Tom Holland / Edward Ruscha: New Works on Paper" (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Current" (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Dangling Dualities" (1979), 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Dennis Evans / Ubu Waugh: Instruments and Diagrams" (1978), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Drawings" (1977), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Eight Seattle Artists" (1980), 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14-17)
    - "Fiber Structures" (1976, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Furniture by Architects" (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "I'm Not Really a Realist Realism Show" (1976), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Images of Women" (1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "In Touch" (1976), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)